what is my trading strategy what is the
secret sauce that Socrates uses my
methodology to trading is so Elementary
it's so simple my daughter is 8 years
old and she pretty much understands the
basics and the concepts of what I do
when I enter the market so uh further
Ado here is my strategy trading strategy
is a system that I put together that
kind of helps me know what I want to
look for when I'm taking my trades now
on the technical side and the charting
side my system is I would be
specifically waiting for the charts or
the price to reach some sort of key
level our previous area where price has
pivoted and that is the only thing that
uh my eyes are looking for on any time
frame is a pivot a break are we near an
area of Supply are we near an area of
demand are we near a daily High a daily
low oh did we touch that London closeth
that New York closeth those are all
potential areas where I could either
Exit or enter trades on any time frame
now when I'm starting my day we start I
start at the weekly then I move down the
weekly the daily the 4 Hour the 1 hour
30 minute the 5 minute lately I have
been taking trades strictly on the 1
hour but mainly I'm looking on the 5
minute to take my entries and my exits
but now that we have the simple side out
of what I look for in trading because
that's pretty much it is once our candle
reaches one of
these one of these key levels are pivots
all I would need to enter the trade then
would be strong volume following suit or
what's happening in the world do is
there earnings is there news is there
some missiles being shot overseas cuz I
mean realistically when we're trading
Futures all of that matters now that we
got theuh technical side of what I
really do my system puts my strategy all
together now what my system is is I go
into every day with a number that I want
to make and a number that I'm willing to
lose a number that I am accepted in my
head that if I hit this it's okay it's
my losing day I'm not going to get upset
and that's how I go I like to take
between one and four trades a day now I
don't have to trade every day but I'm
just giving you a general statement is I
like to take one to four trades a day
and I like to Target between $25 and
$5,000 a day now if I take two losing
trades in a row my trading day is done
and also on all and each and one of my
trading accounts live proper I have a
set number that it it will lock me out
of trading so I can never go below a
certain number and that number is $4,000
so realistically the most money that I
could ever lose in one day is only
$44,000 if I stick to my plan and follow
my rules and trading you're going to
realize it's you're going to waste a lot
of time and money on the wrong sort of
information and [\h__\h] when
realistically the only thing that's ever
happening and why this candle is moving
up and down and we're seeing these
fluctuations is somewhere someone is
pressing this buy button and there it
could be as retail uh Deen Traders but
it's probably a institution and bank
doing it in a calculated manipulated way
this is why I use previous price action
in history aligned with current price
action in history because the market is
the flow of human sentiment and history
always repeats itself and that's
something you will as well learn in your
trading Journey
but uh guys there's a lot of [\h__\h]
and noise so hopefully you know my
content is clearing the air for you now
again I am not I was not born into into
a smart household I was not intelligent
I was a high school dropout I've been to
jail you don't need intelligence to
follow along on the system that I had
created it's not rocket science it's I'm
someone that realizes and no matter what
I'm doing in every trade that I take I
could potentially lose this money that I
could be wrong and it'll put once we
follow once we have our system in place
it kind of alleviates that fear and
stress because if you know you're
someone that okay I can really sit and
listen to myself you're how can you lose
you're only going to lose when you let
greed overtake your picture or overtake
the system or you don't listen to
yourself ultimately every issue that
involves in trading comes back to you
and your mindset and what you do and the
choices that you make if you made $500
within 12 minutes of trading and you
continue to trade come on you know what
I'm saying consistency base hits till we
have that cushion and when we have that
cushion then you can take more risk and
build that buffer up like you really
want but uh yeah that's my tragedy guys
I am not sitting there waiting for fbgs
I'm not sitting there waiting for order
blocks to be filled I'm waiting to touch
specific key levels and now the key
levels that I'm looking for it's an
indicator on trade view that's free
and you I don't change any of the
settings again all I need is volume and
a understanding of the asset that I'm
trading now again I'm trading gold so
some things I could look at while to
help me make decisions our stay in
trades or enter trades or anything
related to it is gold I would be looking
at the dollar the dollar is up gold is
down or we can look at your other metals
maybe silver maybe Platinum uh maybe
copper um you can also look at worldwide
news because gold is a real asset and
the dollar is just paper Monopoly money
but um yeah if you didn't know that go
get yourself a basic education and uh
yeah guys that is my system that is my
strategy and ultimately my strategy only
works if this is here with me what I
mean by that is my mental is on point
I'm confident in the day my emotions are
in check and I'm not letting them get
the best of me I'm not letting greed get
the best of me but ultimately I'm
following my rules that I set for myself
so I will only lose if I do not follow
my rules which would be probably be
greed are you wanting more but uh yeah
give me a like And subscribe if you uh
thought that this video resonated with
what you're trying to hear and give me a
comment below on what you guys want to
see more for me moving forward again
this is probably my fifth video now that
I've posted on a serious note for
YouTube and I would like to continue
doing this but I would love to know what
you guys would like to see personally so
uh thank you for listening hopefully
you'll continue to join it